Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
I'm glad you were all able to attend.
Without further ado, I'd like to commence with the Royal Knight Selection Test.
The exam to decide which knights would fight the Eye of the Midnight Sun had just gotten underway.
When suddenly, a mysterious man appeared on the scene.
So sorry I'm late for the party, everybody!
Who, me? I'm Xerx Lugner. Pleasure's mine.
Despite Asta's immediate distrust of this Xerx, the two of them soon discovered that they had been placed on the same team for the tournament.
And so, in this tense and menacing atmosphere, the Royal Knight Selection Test begins in earnest.
Magic Knights, it's time to start the exam.
Now that the explanations are done, I hope our first two teams are ready.
I was born ready, Your Majesty!
Hm.
Come on!
Thanks, Bobby!
Oh
Asta! Give those guys a beat and they won't forget!
That's right! Show them what the Black Bulls are all about!
Give it your best, okay?
Hurry up and take care of them so you can spar with me later!
Don't be reckless!
I swear I'll take my eyes open for the entire battle online at Blake.
Ah! What kind of interesting spells will I get to see today?
I can't wait to find out!
Here! Anything's more exciting to watch with us!
Why, thank you!
I'm totally psyched now! It's time to do this thing!
Quit shouting already. This is an exam.
You need to stay calm and focus.
Look, the best tactic is to study the terrain and figure out what each of us can offer.
You're right! I hate it, but you're so right!
Everything I say is right, Shortstack, so get used to it.
Settle down now, both of you!
Aw, Asta's cute even when he's gritting his teeth!
I agree with Zerks, though. Let's get familiar with each other's abilities and come up with a solid plan.
I'm sure that's what the other team is doing right now.
Yeah! That's good thinking!
My plant magic is best suited for support and recovery.
And Asta's anti-magic will be useful at close range to nullify the spells our opponents cast.
What kind of magic do you have, Zerks?
What the...?
They're already attacking? So fast! And which direction did it come from?
Either way, I've gotta keep our crystal safe!
Oh no! That looked like a long-distance strike. But how was it so accurate?
I don't understand this. Where's it coming from?
Looks like 10 o'clock, 3 meters. Do you copy?
Roger!
Thanks to a highly precise crystal magic spell called Crystal Scope, their whereabouts are as clear as, well... you know.
I'll make you pay for ridiculing the Wizard King, knave!
You don't deserve a chance to shine after that stunt!
Claim magic, burst javelin!
Combined with rock magic, Strongbow!
We're gonna lose!
Craft, what now? We work together, we...
Seriously, what is the matter with this guy?!
He's terrible!
He's... asleep?
Yep, he's out cold.
Sure looks like it.
Guess he needs a nap.
That's pathetic.
How could anybody fall asleep with all these people watching him?!
The shame! The embarrassment!
My, I never expected a tournament like this to devolve into nap time. They must be worn out. Unless... it's a trick.
What the heck are you laying on the ground for, huh?! If you don't get off your lazy butt right now, our team's crystal is gonna be smashed to pieces!
Do you wanna win this thing or not?! You're such a jerk!
Winning or losing doesn't make a difference to me.
Nor do I care how badly you wanna win. So just direct all that unchecked enthusiasm elsewhere.
Listen, I kinda pulled an all-nighter last night. I'd appreciate it if you two would let me catch a few Z's.
That Zerk's fellow actually has the nerve to sleep.
Do you think it's some kind of strategy?
It's not. My crystal scope can identify not just location, but the physical state of its targets.
There's no doubt that Ruffian is fast asleep.
How can one man be so arrogant, especially after the way he insulted the Wizard King when he first arrived?
That's enough. He's dead!
Whatever his little plan may be, if you don't move, you can't win!
Let's put a stop to this here and now!
Plant creation magic! Magic flower guidepost!
Looks like two of them are close to the crystal, and the other one is 60 meters in front, up in a tree.
The pair's magic is inflated! They must be casting a combo spell!
From that far away? Prepare for another attack!
Right! The last couple were pretty fast, but if I can nail down the direction in time...
Gotcha!
Hiya!
That blast was so quick, I never could have dodged it in time!
Hasta really is amazing!
We don't stand a chance of winning without Zerk's help, though.
It's two against three!
Come on, our best course of action is to leave this guy behind and do what we can on our own!
I can pinpoint the enemy's positions and distract them.
You focus on protecting the crystal.
The two of us are going to charge toward their crystal and hopefully we can destroy it directly.
It's the only option now.
Mimosa's good at thinking fast.
She's been through some really tough battles, that's for sure.
Alright! That's what we'll do!
Our first team effort is going great, huh?
It is our first.
I'm glad.
Let's go!
Here it comes!
Look at that!
Those two are running straight toward the target!
That guy's got some guts!
Too bad their teammate's taking a nap.
Is he trying to pull something?
Maybe.
But whether it works or not is going to depend on their abilities.
Do you actually find this interesting?
A date with me would have been a lot more fun, but somebody couldn't be bothered to go!
What's with that face?
Doesn't anything get to you?
That's it, Mr. Guppy, I'm gonna force you to smile!
You know, those two actually make a good team.
I mean, not that it matters to me whatsoever.
You can do this. Both of you, be strong!
What's that boy thinking?
He's blocking all our combo spells as he rushes in, crystal in tow.
It would appear he's planning to strike us head on.
One of them must be tracking our location as well.
They're coming closer.
Up there!
They're guarding the crystal!
That's them!
We have nothing to fear.
After all, our crystal is completely untouched, and theirs is already quite damaged.
Plant magic!
Huh?
Rock magic!
Magic Cannon Flower!
Rock Fortress!
Oh, wow, Mimosa!
I didn't know you could do any super cool attack spells!
Asta, I'm going to get stronger.
The next time we face an enemy together, I'll be able to fight by your side!
I'll take the lead now, Asta.
Let's turn this around!
We may be down a teammate, but we can still win!
Awesome! I can really count on this girl!
I know just what to do!
Magic Cannon Flower!
Man, check her out!
So she's not just a pretty face, but she's powerful too?
Yeah! It's love!
She's the total package!
That's fantastic!
Oh, wow!
I wonder if she'll let me spar with her!
Hmm...
That cute little flower's really starting to bloom.
It's probably because she's working with Asta.
I can't believe she's able to fight so boldly in front of such a huge audience!
Isn't she weird?
Wow, she's good!
During my training, I noticed your improvement, but now that you're here, I can see how much progress you've made on your journey!
As your superior, I'm very proud of you!
She's giving this all she's got!
I have to start taking things more seriously!
I'm not losing to her!
Nice work, Mimosa!
What was that?
You smiled for me, didn't you?
Well, help! I finally got what I wanted!
I'm not smiling.
You're just seeing things.
You have to have the last word, don't you?
But hey, I don't necessarily dislike that about you.
Good!
And she's got a fair amount of room to grow as well!
Go Asta!
You can do it!
And if you win, I'll give you a tasty snack!
They're missing their third man.
Perhaps it's best to approach and overpower them.
Not yet.
The weapon that boy is holding is an anti-magic sword.
I saw its power.
There will be no defeating it in close quarters combat.
What? Anti-magic?
I'd heard rumors, but he's the one who wields it?
It would be foolish to engage him too casually.
Well then?
Hmm.
They split up!
But which one has the crystal?
The magic flower guidepost!
Judging from this.
Aim for the left!
You got it!
That's it, boy!
You're no match for me!
That's a huge power concentration!
Careful!
The next attack will be enormous!
Then I'll have to slice through that and the crystal too!
What?
Two identical reactions?
The other two are preparing a heavy mid-range attack!
Which means...
We're surrounded!
If even one of those spells hits our crystal, it won't survive the damage!
Asta might be able to take them on one at a time, but we're done for if they all strike at once!
Asta!
They've got him!
It's a trap!
Is that...?
So one of them can use paralyzing trap magic?
No!
Where did they come from?
We can't be sure of anything!
This test is more rigorous than I expected!
Do it now!
From three directions?
They can't dodge that!
They're trapped like rats!
Oh dear!
This doesn't look good!
It doesn't look good!
What happened to our magic?
Oh...
Oh dear...
Oh, what happened to our magic?
Our spells are being sent straight back at us!
What kind of ability was that?
I... I'm not sure.
Asta!
Well, looks like everything worked out okay.
I... I don't understand this!
Should've known. I thought that last attack would've shattered your crystal, but I suppose you are a senior magic knight after all.
So you managed to keep it from crumbling apart and stopped yourself from going unconscious.
What a good boy.
Unfortunately, though, it seems you and your precious crystal are on your last legs.
And since you never know what surprises might be lurking around the corner, it's in my best interest to destroy said crystal.
What a good magic knight is supposed to be prepared for any possibility.
You should know you can't win by throwing a tantrum and firing off a bunch of heavy-duty attacks.
Pal, if you lost to me, you're no magic knight at all.
I'll kill you!
His magic... it's Ash-type!
That means the trap magic that Asta before must've been his doing.
This has been fun, but I'm bored.
Better luck next time, you piece of garbage!
Damn it all!
You know what, on second thought.
I may not have come here to win, but I do have a very specific purpose in mind.
What's the meaning of this?
Just kidding, loser.
The crystal's magic has been cut off!
Team B's the winner!
What kind of power does that guy have, anyway?
It amplified his enemy's magic and sent it right back at him!
I couldn't make much sense of it, but that was most impressive!
The Masked Man's Royal Knight's material!
He's my first pick!
I'm glad Asta's team won the first match, but I'm frustrated at the same time!
Then again, all it takes to make me feel better is a little more food!
Hey, we were pretty solid back there.
Teamwork really does make the dream work, right?
You were the best decoys a guy could ask for.
I mean, did you see his face?
He was so sure I wasn't gonna break that thing.
Thanks, Mimosa.
Uh, sure.
Look, mister!
I've had enough of your attitude!
You can't treat a fellow Magic Knight like that!
Their team fought hard and did a good job!
So what if they did?
A loss is a loss.
At the end of the day, we had better teamwork, so we wiped the floor with them.
Be happy, you little run.
No really, teamwork!
Listen to you!
That trap I walked into near the end was created by your magic, wasn't it?
How could you do that to your own teammate?
I just needed you to serve as the decoy to set it off.
You know what they say.
To trick your foes, you gotta start with your friends.
Who says that?
Oh.
And I've got one more surprise for you in my collar.
Why do you keep tricking me?
You're the worst!
Jeez, my eyes feel like they're burning!
I'm...
Man, I swear that never gets old.
I think I see now.
He draws a magic circle somewhere on the terrain or on an object and infuses it with the power
of a spell.
Then as soon as certain conditions are met, the trap is triggered.
Correct.
Near the end of the battle, Asta inadvertently activated a trap designed to target any opposing
spells infiltrating that territory within a predetermined time period.
This ability is known as counter-trap magic.
It doubles the speed and power of any spells it reflects, so the stronger the foes attack,
the more deadly the result.
For such a large-scale trap magic spell, you'd need massive amounts of time and magic power.
When did you manage to do it?
After all, you were sleeping for most of the fights.
I kind of prefer to stay mysterious.
That guy sucks.
I'll give you mysterious, you big jerk!
I'll knock that super cool mask right off your face, you hear me?
I think it'd be more convincing if you didn't compliment him.
Come back here and tell us everything right now!
Or I'll punch you!
Give it a rest, Asta.
Seriously, do you have to be so loud 24-7?
You guys have had your fun, and now it's our turn to tear it up.
Move aside, would ya?
You know, you're kind of cocky for a twerp with ugly purple glasses.
They're not ugly, they're cool, and you just wish you had some too!
I don't have to take this crap from you, giant girl!
You only think I'm giant because you're so short and wimpy.
Who are you calling wimpy?
I'll make you eat those words.
Oh, hey, it's Magna!
And giant girl!
Wait, where's your third member?
Honestly, every last one of you is desperately devoid of style.
Ugh, kill me!
My, what an eyesore!
I'll thank you not to interfere with the splendor of the magnificent Kirsch Vermillion.
Okay, why is he sparkling?
Did he say Vermillion?
Sadly, this is my older brother.
For real?
I wish I wasn't.
I'm so beautiful!
Oh, I can't stand it!
He kind of brightens everything up, doesn't he?
I'd be much happier if he disappeared.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
Oh!
僕らの誓いはここにある
口ずさむ合言葉は
I'll make it true
My song, my days
この世界に響かせいこう
駆け抜けた日々をいつか誇るまで
僕らなら諦めない
My song, my days
音符を書き加えてく
曲がりくなった道さの暗には
輝ける明日を映すメロディー
クロークリプス
The next time we meet
Asta, I'm going to get stronger
The next time we face an enemy together
I'll be able to fight by your side
I'm strong
You've got this, Mimosa
So strong
Almost there, Mimosa
Yeah
And so
Asta, I've gotten much stronger
Here I go
Gots
You can
Wow, that was amazing
Where did you learn to surf like that, Mimosa?
I did it!
I am the beautiful Kirsch Vermillion, Mimosa's beautiful older brother
Are you blinded by my beauty?
Terribly sorry, I can't help it
Beautiful black clover, beautiful page 75, fierce battle
Don't hate me because I'm beautiful